secure256.com 2018-08-17

# Privacy Policy for CPASiteSolutions Websites for CPAs and Accountants

  1. Home
  2. CPA Site Solutions' Privacy Policy

## Collection

* * *

This Privacy Policy describes how we handle your personal information for our services on the CPASiteSolutions websites.

CPASiteSolutions collects certain information from and about its users three ways: (i) from our web server logs, (ii) with cookies and (iii) directly from the user.

**_Web Server Logs_**  
When you visit our website, CPASiteSolutions may collect information to administer the site and analyze its usage. CPASiteSolutions may collect information such as:

  * Your Internet protocol address; 
  * The type of browser or computer you use; 
  * The number of links you click within our website; 
  * The state or country from which you accessed our website; 
  * The date and time of your visit; 
  * The name of your Internet service provider; 
  * The Web page from which you linked to our website; and 
  * The pages you viewed on our website

**_Cookies_**  
CPASiteSolutions' websites use cookies (i.e., small bits of text that our servers place into a file on your computer's hard drive). We use cookies to save your preferences and login information, and provide personalized functionality. You can reject cookies by changing your browser settings, but be aware that this will disable some of the functionality on CPASiteSolutions's website.

**_Personal Information Users Give Us_**  
On some pages of our website, users can subscribe to services and information, during this process CPASiteSolutions may ask you for some personal information.

As a security measure and to ensure that our website and computer network remain available to all interested users, CPASiteSolutions may use software programs to monitor network traffic or to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage. These software programs may also collect information regarding your use of our website and computer network.

You may also be asked to disclose personal information to us so that we can provide technical support assistance and information to you. For example, we may collect personal information from you, such as an e-mail address, system information and problem descriptions, in order to provide online technical support and troubleshooting. If you choose to correspond with us through electronic communication, such as email, we may retain a copy of the electronic communication together with your email address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received by mail and telephone.

## Access to Your Information

* * *

CPASiteSolutions will share or disclosure your personal data:

  * As required by law, in a matter of public safety or policy, or as compelled by a court of law;
  * As needed in connection with the transfer of business assets.

## Links to Other Websites

* * *

CPASiteSolutions's website contains links to sites maintained by other companies that are not affiliated with CPASiteSolutions. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those sites, and we encourage you to use caution when visiting them. In particular, we recommend you view the privacy policy posted on each site

## How We Use Your Information

* * *

CPASiteSolutions uses the information we collect to notify you about your account and to notify you about changes to the terms and conditions governing your use of our website and services. We may also use the information we collect to notify you about other products and services we think you will find valuable and about special offers.

## How We Protect Your Information

* * *

CPASiteSolutions uses advanced technical and physical security measures to prevent the loss, misuse, alteration or unauthorized disclosure of information under our control. See CPASiteSolutions Security Measures.

**_Account Protection_**  
Your password is the key to your account. Use unique numbers, letters and special characters, and do not disclose your CPASiteSolutions password to anyone. If you do share your password or your personal information with others, remember that you are responsible for all actions taken in the name of your account. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personal information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately notify CPASiteSolutions and change your password.

**_Security_**  
Your information is stored on our servers located in the United States. We treat data as an asset that must be protected and use lots of tools (encryption, passwords, physical security, etc.) to protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure. However, as you probably know, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, and other users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from the site. Therefore, although we work very hard to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.

**_Client Financial Information_**  
The CPASiteSolutions' Portal enables your clients to store and share their personal and financial information with you. We take extreme measures to protect your client's data (See CPASiteSolutions Security Measures). However, as you probably know, third parties may unlawfully intercept or otherwise gain access to private data. Therefore, although we work very hard to protect your client's data, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your client's personal information or private communications will always remain private. So, we encourage you to disclose your own privacy and security practices to your clients.

## General

* * *

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amended terms on this site. All amended terms automatically take effect 30 days after they are initially posted on the Site. If you have any comments or questions regarding this Privacy Policy please contact CPASiteSolutions via email at [support@cpasitesolutions.com](mailto:support@cpasitesolutions.com). This Privacy Policy is effective upon acceptance for new users and is otherwise effective on June 4, 2007.

**Get your website up with only 10 minutes of your time.**  
(We'll spend hours on it so you don't have to.)
